kindercare.com 2007-12-21

# KinderCare : Privacy Policy

_Last Modified: July 11, 2005_

KinderCare® understands the importance of protecting the privacy of all KinderCare customers, including visitors to KinderCare.com. We believe that, as our online visitor, you have the right to know our practices regarding the information we collect when you visit our website, and what type of information is collected. To help ensure a rewarding online experience for all visitors, we provide this summary of our information practices.

These guidelines only apply to your visits to KinderCare.com, which is operated by KinderCare Learning Centers, Inc. Other websites that are linked to or from KinderCare.com may have different policies; therefore, please review the privacy policy notices on those websites for details.

##  The Information We Collect

Through this site, KinderCare collects two kinds of information: general information and personal information.

**General information** is not specific to you and cannot be traced in any way to you. Such information includes certain non-personal information from visitors to the site (such as the time of day the site is accessed) and certain information in aggregate form (such as statistics relating to the number and frequency of visitors). 

KinderCare also uses the technology called "cookies", which involves placing a small text file on your computer. The cookie assigns a unique identifying number to your web browser, allowing the KinderCare.com site to recognize your browser (but not otherwise identify you) and passively track activities on the site. Data collected from Kindercare.com cookies is general data and used only in the aggregate; our cookies do not access, collect, or reveal any personal information or other data stored on your computer.

Also, KinderCare, or third parties on its behalf, may collect anonymous information from visits to our sites through the use of "Web Beacons." Web Beacons are electronic images that enable us to record anonymous data about visits to our web site. We may use this data to analyze statistics to improve our customer service. No personal data is collected through the use of Web Beacons on our sites.

Personal information is specific to you and includes such things as your e-mail address, name, and mailing address. This type of information is sometimes called "personally identifiable information." The only personal information collected through the KinderCare.com site is information you choose to supply in response to a request or offer.

KinderCare has designed this site for parents and adult caregivers, not children. For that reason, KinderCare does not knowingly collect personal information from children who may visit this site, and KinderCare does not want to include any such information in its customer databases. We recommend that parents monitor their children's use of the Internet.

##  How We Use the Information

KinderCare uses general information only in ways that do not identify you, the specific user, which means that it is never linked to personal information. In order to improve our site and to better serve you, KinderCare may share your personal information with its subsidiaries, affiliates, legal successors, and trusted third parties. From time to time, KinderCare may also contact you about updates or special offers.

##  Changes in Privacy Policy

The terms of this policy will apply to any information collected while it is in place. KinderCare may change its privacy policy from time to time in its sole discretion, and if our privacy policy changes, we will change this statement and post those changes here to keep you informed about how we treat your personal information. Feel free to check our privacy statement for current updates whenever you visit this site. In case of any material change, we will make a notation near the "Privacy Policy" link on the home page of KinderCare.com.

##  Contact Us

If you wish to review and/or request changes to your personally identifiable information collected at KinderCare.com, you have the following options:

  1. You can send an e-mail to our Customer Service Department at [ customercare@klcorp.com](mailto:customercare@klcorp.com).
  2. You can send regular mail correspondence to the following address: 

Knowledge Learning Corporation  
650 NE Holladay Street, Suite 1400  
PO Box 6760  
Portland, OR 97228

  3. You can call the following telephone number toll-free:   
1 (888) 525-2780 

If you have any further questions, comments, or concerns regarding this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, please contact the webmaster at:

Webmaster  
Knowledge Learning Corporation  
650 NE Holladay Street, Suite 1400  
PO Box 6760  
Portland, Oregon 97228
